## **Naveed Khan**

Sr. Media Buyer

https://www.linkedin.com/in/naveedmediabuver/

E-Mail: paidmediabuyer@gmail.com

Mobile: +92 3087405040 Address: New Tariq Abad Khanewal Road Multan,

Pakistan.

### **Summary**

I am an "Expert Media Buyer". I specialize in marketing with a special place in my heart for Digital Marketing. I have 4 years of experience in Facebook Ads, Google Ads, Google Shopping Ads, Youtube Ads. Tik Tok Ads.

I enjoy researching diverse cultures around the globe. It enables me to determine the best and most relevant audience for the campaigns of my clients. I am always engaged on social media and keep up with the latest trends across multiple platforms.

#### **Recent Clients Handled:**

- Shahid Afridi Foundation
- Aghosh UK
- Sparko Sol
- Faisal Movers Housing

### **Expertise & Certifications:**

- Facebook Ads, Google Ads, Shopping Ads
- Youtube Ads, Display Ads, Linkedin Ads, Twitter Ads
- Tik Tok Ads, Youtube SEO, Google Merchant Center
- Google Analytics. Google Tag Manager

## **Work Experience:**



## Sr. Media Buyer

Sparko Sol October 2022 – January 2024

- Set up, monitor, and optimize Facebook, Google advertising campaigns from start to finish.
- Analyze media buys and associated metrics daily to ensure profitability.
- A/B test ad copy, images/videos, and funnels effectively to meet performance goals.
- Analyze web metrics, provide campaign effectiveness reports, and implement optimizations.
- Generate Targeted Leads, Sales (e-commerce)
- Perform competitive research on effective ads in similar niches.
- Create weekly and monthly reports
- New strategies based on data and testing

Working with the team to assess and improve overall marketing performance



# **Digital Marketing Executive**Faisal Movers Housing (Multan, Pakistan)

Jan 2022 – Jan 2023

- Build and launch Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, Linkedin, Google, Display, and Youtube Ads.
- Help create weekly and monthly reports
- Recommend new strategies based on data and testing
- Launch and monitor Ads
- Help with new emerging channels.
- Work with other departments (e.g. product development, creative, and merchandising) to ensure goal and strategy alignment, as well as to maintain brand identity
- Do Google Analytics analysis
- Help set up processes



## **Digital Marketing Executive**

Faisal Cottages (Multan, Pakistan) Oct 2020 – November 2022

- Build and launch Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, Linkedin, Google, Display, and Youtube Ads.
- Help create weekly and monthly reports

- Recommend new strategies based on data and testing
- Launch and monitor Ads
- Help with new emerging channels.
- Work with other departments (e.g. product development, creative, and merchandising) to ensure goal and strategy alignment, as well as to maintain brand identity
- Do Google Analytics analysis
- Help set up processes



**Digital Marketing Executive** Hateem City (Multan, Pakistan) Jan 2022 – Jan 2023

- Build and launch Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, Linkedin, Google, Display, and Youtube Ads.
- Help create weekly and monthly reports
- Recommend new strategies based on data and testing
- Launch and monitor Ads
- Help with new emerging channels.
- Work with other departments (e.g. product development, creative, and merchandising) to ensure goal and strategy alignment, as well as to maintain brand identity
- Do Google Analytics analysis
- Help set up processes

#### **Education:**

- Bachelor in Arts from B.Z.U Multan in 2014
- D.A.E Civil from P.B.T.E Lahore in 2010
- Matriculation from B.I.S.E Multan in 2007